Dylan Couzon

Full stack Web Developer

I'm a hard-working, methodical, and resourceful Full-stack web developer looking for a job in the Tech industry. I'm passionate about puzzles and problem solving, and been coding as a hobby for over 12 years. My work experience in London, Australia, France, and now San Francisco bestowed me with great adaptability and Teamwork skills

dylancouzon@gmail.com 🔀

(510) 513-9155

San Francisco Q

linkedin.com/in/dcouzon in

github.com/Dylancouzon

SKILLS

HTML/CSS

Photoshop

Berkeley

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web development

UC Berkeley Extension

06/2021

GPA 4.0

 Intense certificate in HTML/CSS, Git, JavaScript(jQuery, React, node), AJAX, MERN, SQL(MySQL, MongoDB)

PERSONAL PROJECTS

FarQuest (05/2021)

 A role-playing game of medieval fantasy. Select from a hero class of Knights, Wizards, Huntresses, or be an Assassin. Explore a rich world of story-telling, battles, and surprises as you journey to see the King. He's asked for your help and you fear you're running out of time.

Feriale.fr (2010 - 2012)

- Created a Full-Stack client interface allowing users to create an account, join the game, manage their account, and buy upgrades or additional items for their online characters which resulted in
- Set up an admin interface allowing to communicate with the community and provide support to members
- Successfully maintained and kept improving the website for 2 years
- Installed, maintained the Unix server with over 99.7% uptime

WORK EXPERIENCE

Production manager

Mademoiselle Colette Inc. 01/2020 - 03/2021

Newark, CA

Managed the workflow of a team of 20+ people and training of new hires. Ensured that all the products were up to company standard, as well as meeting deadlines and customers expectations

Pastry Chef Citi Bank

01/2018 - 08/2019

London, UK

Managed the pastry production for 2 restaurants and an executive kitchen inside Citi Bank HQ. Created bespoke menus for VIP customers

LANGUAGES

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency